androidegis.com 2014-12-18

# AndroidEgis | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Android Egis** love to protect the policy that enables you to know about the way we use to work. We try to share terms and conditions in a simple manner so that you can easily work with us. Technologies seem like an important factor of life and we make your life easy by giving your information related to Android devices and software. We love to share Android apps, news, how to, tips and tricks, Android mobiles and other things regarding your Android’s life. Android Egis team is conscious to give users’ complete protection from all edges.

## Cookies And Web Beacons

We can use cookies to record information about the preference of use on various parts to get information about your needs.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google uses cookies to serve ads, they use DART cookie for ads, and you can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense)  and [Amazon](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/).  
We do not have control on cookies of third-party advertiser, many browsers accept cookies automatically but you can get rid of them from your browser setting. You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

## Getting Your Personal Information

Keep in mind that we need your information on various parts like IP address, language, operating time and browser type might be collected automatically as a part of the site operation. Even we can get navigational information like what you are viewing to know about your interests. However you should not be worried about your information as it’s secure and we just use info to maintain site preference that helps you to get more. Also we use the detail to contact you through various means such as marketing communication materials, sends email, newsletter and the latest promotions. We keep your record in specific areas where it is absolutely safe. We don’t use it for illegal purpose but just use it to fulfill the blank and required area. Android Egis does not share the info with anyone, we just use it fulfill your requirements.

## Copyright

Android Egis is a web blog and it’s completely dedicated to Android operating system. We love to share Android apps, news, how-to, tips and tricks, Android mobiles and other things regarding your Android’s life. We love to produce helping stuff and dedicate everything to Android. We give proper credit to everything we use in our web blog such as images, files, apps, media, etc. We take copyright issues very seriously. We are well-aware with **DMCA terms and conditions** and hate illegal copyrighted content. We follow all of DMCA terms and conditions. You do not have right to copy anything from Android Egis, if you do this, you will have to face the music as we will file **DCMA take down notice**.

## Content

We link all of suggestions, opinions, media, articles, images, etc. to original resources. We do not try to share misleading detail but if you still find us wrong on any step, you may [contact us](http://www.androidegis.com/contact-us/). With lots of combinations of configurations and updates of software, we are unable to give everything free from risk.

## Modifications to This Privacy Policy

Android Egis can modify this privacy policy at any time depending on DMCA, Google and other cyber terms and conditions; however we should inform you about changes at the top.

## Contact Us

You may ask questions through emails as well as use emails for all kind of queries.
